https://globalpartnerships.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Global Partnerships (GP) is committed to respecting the privacy of our online visitors. GP only collects personal information that you choose to share with us when signing up to receive newsletters or email updates, or making charitable contributions. Any information collected on our website is used solely by GP for internal purposes or to communicate with you in accordance with your preferences. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your authorization. If our policy changes in the future, you will be notified and the changes will be posted here. If at any time you wish to discontinue receiving email updates from us, simply click on the unsubscribe link in your email, or contact us at the phone number, address or email address below.
Our online donations are processed through a third-party service, Blackbaud, Inc., which is a VeriSign-authorized vendor. You will be asked to provide your name, contact information and credit card billing information. All of this information is encrypted using industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology, as is all information on our website.
All personal information gathered by GP is stored on our server, and access is controlled via Active Directory security so that only authorized users are allowed access to various directories and files. The GP network is protected by a firewall that controls all access to the network. All users of any level are issued a user name and complex password for their access to the network on our server.
If you have any questions regarding our policy, or if you wish to review personal information we may have on file or request corrections to mail and email addresses, please contact us:
Global Partnerships
1932 First Avenue, Suite 400
Seattle, WA 98101 USA
Phone: 206.652.8773
Email: info@globalpartnerships.org
